Guide to the Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
  - "Sing America", July 2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Jamestown 2007 O'Connor, April 3, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - DOJ (Department of Justice) / OT (overtime pay) for ATTY's, November 14, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Moussaoi / Court TV, May 2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Capital Punishment, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - COPS (Office of Community Policing Services) DOJ (Department of Justice), August 22, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Guns, 107th, July 2001 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Illegal Gun Task Force, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - MS-13 (La Mara Salvatrucha), 2006 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - BATF (Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives Reform Act) Overhaul, May-June 2008 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Federal Marriage Amendment, September 2004 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Same Sex Marriage, September 2006 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - ED (Education), Title 1 Distribution, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Foreign student data, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - FFCO (Fairfax County) Public Schools (2005 Legislative Program), December 2004 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - College Cost Reduction Act, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Title 1 Funding FCPS (Fairfax County Public Schools), 2004 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - NCLB (No Child Left Behind), 2004 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Illegal Gun Force Hearing, April 14, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Federal Employees 105th, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - AAJs (Administrative Appeals Judges) pay, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Air America CSRS (Civil Service Retirement System), 2005 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - H.R. 994 score, June 28, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - H.R. 960, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - ORR (Office of Regulations and Rulings) / Telecommuting, February 27, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - NTEU (National Treasury Employees Union) Telework, February 8, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - NSPS (National Security Personnel System), 2007 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Security Clearances, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Sandy Berger, Undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Design-Build letter, May 24, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Ship Builders Caucus, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Norfolk Aircraft Carrier, February 2005 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Concurrent Receipt, February 2002 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Co-signed letters, 107th Congress, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Finance, 1999-2002 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Faith-based(organizations), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Voting Rights Act, July 12, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Campaign Finance (Reform), 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - GOP Unity Coalition, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - FSDEF (The Free Speech Defense & Education Fund), 2007 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Immigration press, March 11, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Immigration: 245(i) (undocumented immigrants seeking visa), March 12-13, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Immigration: TPS (Temporary Protected Status), 2002 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Immigration: TPS (Temporary Protected Status) for Guatemala, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Immigration: AgJOBS (Agricultural Jobs, Opportunities, Benefits, and Security Act) H.R. 3142, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - KKK regulation, September-October 2007 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Immigration, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Ramos and Compean border patrol, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Issue summary, Forpol (Foreign Policy), January 2003 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Iraq resolution, July 2007 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Iraq oil revenue sharing, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Republican Israel Caucus, January 25, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Microfinance, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Amnesty International / Turkmenistan letter, February-March 2006 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Iraq: Fresh Eyes, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Panama, Salvador trip (includes photographs and hard disks), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Project Hope, Romanian Orphans, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Korean Cable TV, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Iraq, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - El Salvador, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Egypt speech, May 2002 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Bolivia, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - China, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Community outreach / annual events, 1998, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, June 2007 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding social security and medicare, June 2007 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Real ID, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, June-July 2007 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding H.R. 2353 Cancer Screening, Treatment, and Survivorship Act of 2007, May 2007 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Co-sponsor creation of Office of Men's Health, June 2007 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding corn-based ethanol, May-June 2007 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding H.R. 2635 Carbon Neutral Government Act, June 19, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding H.R. 2593 Borderlands Conservation and Security Act, June 2007 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding H.R. 1766 CHESSA Bill, April-June 2007 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding H.R. 2419 Farm Bill Extension Act of 2007 [section 123], June-July 2007 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Sanders-Boxer Global Warming Pollution Reduction Act; Waxman Safe Climate Act, June-July 2007 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding H.R. 2419 Farm Bill, July 2007 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Congressional Immigration Reform Caucus, June-July 2007 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding immigration - H.R. 4313 TRUE Enforcement and Border Security Act of 2005, June 14, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Pro-immigration Law Reform, June 2007 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding S. 1348/1639 Comprehensive Immigration (Bush/Kennedy Compromise), June 2007 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - NACARA (Nicaraguan Adjustment and Central American Relief Act), 2002 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Mr. Mintoo, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Davis's schedule, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Davis's schedule, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from Davis, January 2007-March 2008 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail reply letters (TOC (table of contents) #1-#118) 1 of 4, Circa 2006-2008 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Constituent mail reply letters (#119-#180) 2 of 4, Circa 2006-2008 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Constituent mail reply letters (#181-#266) 3 of 4, Circa 2006-2008 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Constituent mail reply letters (#267-#380) 4 of 4, Circa 2006-2008 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Fairness in Representation Act (D.C. FAIR Act) briefing materials, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Fairfax Sun Gazette article - "The Politician" by Liza Mundy (not foldered), March 8, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Virginia baseball, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Baseball, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Three letters from Davis - two on behalf of the Fairfax County Water Authority, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Korea, Non immigrant visas, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Energy and Commerce Commission 107th Congress, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Davis's schedule, 1996, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Congress Online Project: E-mail overload in Congress (not foldered), 2001 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Congressman Davis issues updates newsletters, 1997-2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Constituent mail with response, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Constituent mail with response, October 2003 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Request for Presidential greeting cards, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Constituent mail with response, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Constituent mail with response, August 2003 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Constituent mail with response, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Constituent mail with response, July 2003 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Constituent mail with response, June-August 2003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Constituent mail with response, June 30-July 1, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Constituent mail with response, June 2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Constituent mail with response, June 2003 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Congressional Record, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Letters, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Congressional Record; Sports articles, December 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Constituent mail with response, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Constituent mail with response, May-June 2003 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Constituent mail with response, May 2003 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Constituent mail with response, May-June 2003 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Constituent mail with response, June 2003 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Constituent mail with response, September-October 2003 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Constituent mail with response, April 7-11, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Constituent mail with response, March 31-April 4, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Constituent mail with response, March 24-28, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Constituent mail with response, March 17-21, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Constituent mail with response, March 10-14, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Constituent mail with response, March 3, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Constituent mail with response, February 24-27, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Constituent mail with response, February 17-21, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Constituent mail with response, February 10-14, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Constituent mail with response, February 3-7, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Constituent mail with response, January 27-31, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Constituent mail with response, January 20-24, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Constituent mail with response, January 13-17, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Constituent mail with response, January 6-10, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Constituent mail with response, January 1-3, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - First Baptist Church of Vienna, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Congressional Record, December 2001 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Congressional Record, April 2002 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Constituent mail with response, April 21-24, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Constituent mail with response, April 28-May 2, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Federal Employee/Retiree speech (not foldered), Undated (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - GSA's Telecommuting Pilot Program, Circa 1998 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Davis statements (not foldered), 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Charles W. Sanders, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - David H. Hillman (SMC) (Southern Management Corporation), 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Amherst Newsletter. (The Amherst Spectator), May 1997 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Five miscellaneous letters (not foldered), 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Dr. James Storrs letter, July 24, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - 203K Program, May 1997 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - NEA (National Endowment of the Arts)/NEH (National Endowment for the Humanities) / NPR / CPB, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Farmland Protection Act (blue folder), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Commission on U.S. Capitol preservation, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Dornan issues, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Persian Gulf War Veterans Health Act of 1998; Drugs and Informed Consent Armed Forces Protection Act (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - USS Indianapolis Bill, H.R. 3710, June 1998 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - VA (Virginia) miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Hmong Veterans Naturalization Act. H.R. 371, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Veterans Medicare Option Bill, H.R. 1362, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - H.R. 3613, April 1998 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Persian Gulf War Veterans Health and Medical Research Act, April-June 1998 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Commission on Veterans affairs. H.R. 335, April, June 1997 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - H.R. 4035, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - FEHBP (Federal Employees Health Benefits Program), May 19, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Millennium Society Act, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Veterans Cemetery Protection Act, H.R. 1532, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Volunteer Protection Act, H.R. 911, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Music Licensing Act, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Cold War Memorial, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Capitol Preservation Committee, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Paycheck Protection Act, H.R. 2608, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - Labor miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Public Safety Employer-Employee Cooperation Act, H.R. 1173, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Federal Firefighters Pay Fairness Act of 1997, H.R. 1166 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Hughes-Emerson Commission on Alcoholism, H.R. 1549, May 1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Volunteer Firefighter Equipment Enhancement Act, H.R. 2523, September 1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - H.R. 59, National Right to Work, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Ergonomics / Bonilla language, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Job Corps Letter, Davis statement, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 758/5325 Anti-Salting Bill, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Letters concerning volunteering, workplace policies and tax law (not foldered), May-July 1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Two manila envelopes: Cold War Memorial bill in both, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Missing Service Personnel Act, H.R. 409, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Two letters, one on POW/MIA flag, one on Support Veterans Home Loan Options (not foldered), 1997 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Medicare Subvention, January 1997 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Persian Gulf Veto, H.R. 250, January 7, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Representative Watts, Medicare part B Penalty for Military Retirees, March-April 1997 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Purple Heart Legislation, H.R. 1407, March-April 1997 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Filipino Veterans Equity Act, H.R. 836, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - VA (Virginia) Disabled Compensation, H.R. 303 and H.R. 65, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - H.R. 598, Medicare Part B, March-April 1997 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - 1995 National Youth Gang Survey (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Two CRS reports for Congress on violence and youths, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Study of Youth Gangs in Virginia report, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Fairfax County, Community Audit of Youth Services, January 1997 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Fax cover sheets; 6 CRS reports on Juvenile crime (not foldered), 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - CRS reports on youth violence, July, October 1997 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Letters, 1996, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - H.R. 4244 (blue folder), August 1998 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - H.R. 3921 (blue folder), 1998 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Subcommittee on Government Management (blue folder), 1998 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Reports including 1996 Coalition Book (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Moorefield Visitors Center, January 1996 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Moorefield House, November 1996 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Lilyan Spero, Citizen of the Year CR, March 1997 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - W.S. (West Springfield) Lady Sportaus, April 1997 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - FX (Fairfax) Ch. Of Com. (Chamber of Commerce) valor awards, CR (includes diskette), 1997 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Best of Reston, CR, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Juanita White, CR, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Norman M. Cole Jr. CR, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Dale City Civic Association, CR, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - P.W. (Prince William) Ch. Of Commerce (Chamber of Commerce) valor awards, CR, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - CAGE (?) (Constituent mail with response), 1996 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Colonels Spencer and Sheffield, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Toyota packet. (Chip N.), June 12, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - U.S. House of Representatives: Results of the Customer Satisfaction Survey, July 18, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Government Applications task force: Pilot projects, Circa 1990s (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Information services: BNC (Bankruptcy Noticing Center), August 11, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Subcommittee on Government Management (blue folder), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Subcommittee on Government Management (blue folder), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - D.C. finances (blue folder), 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - D.C. finances (blue folder), 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Department of Commerce, NTIS (National Technical Information Service) (blue folder), Circa 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 4579, Taxpayer Relief Act of 1998 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Balanced Budget Act of 1997, July 1997 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Tax deduction for self-employed (health insurance), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 1084, The Lifetime Tax Reduction Act, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - IITRI (IIT Research Institute) letter, September-November 1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 3879, Estate Tax, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - National Summit on Retirement Savings, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Women, general, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Women, domestic violence, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - VA (Virginia) Personal Property Tax Relief Act of 1998, October 1998 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Budget Surplus Information, March 1998 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Treatment of Women in Afghanistan, 1996-1998 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Women in workforce statistics, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - VAWA (Violence Against Women Act), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - TOV (Northern Virginia Turn Off the Violence Coalition) 1998 information (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Child Care Info, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Child Support Enforcement, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Child Support Enforcement info, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - TOV (Northern Virginia Turn Off the Violence Coalition) 1999, 4th Year (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - NBCC (National Breast Cancer Coalition) voting information and preliminary dear colleagues, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Kinsey Institute info, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - CRS (Congressional Research Service) Adoption Information, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Daniel Love casework, June 29, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - H.R. 99, December 1998 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - WIC (Women, Infants, and Children) feeding the poor CRS (Congressional Research Service) Information, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - VA (Virginia) Inc (income) tax credit for welfare recipients, September 1998 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - House Concurrent Res (Resolution) 182, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Safe and Healthy Motherhood Act, May 13, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - H.R. 3779, May 6, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Dod (Department of Defense) Breast Cancer Research letter, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Reports and bill summaries mostly regarding violence against women (not foldered ), 1997 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - VA (Virginia) Birth Related Injury Compensation Program, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - VA (Virginia) Birth Related Injury Compensation Program (not foldered), May 1, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Project Children, November-December 1998 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - General articles; Clinton Child Abuse proposals, 106th, December 30, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - VA (Virginia) welfare info, December 15, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Hope for Children Act info, October 1998 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - H.R. 1946, Parental Rights Act, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - CDF (Children's Defense Fund), Child care profile in VA (Virginia), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - H. Con. Res. (House Concurrent Resolution 267) on Space, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Benefit plan for military retirees (February 19, 1998); National Research Investment Act of 1998 (not foldered) (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Science Committee letter on China by Pres. Clinton, June 1998 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Committee on Science (not foldered), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Mir Hearing, September 18, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Letters concerning multiple bills (not foldered), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - H.R. 2767, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - NCSSMA (National Council of Social Security Management Associations), federal overtime for supervisors, policy reform, April 10, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Jewish War Vets stamp, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Balanced Budget (blue folder), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Federal Advisory Committee Act (June 1998); Correspondence mostly regarding RIF (Reduction in Force) at U.S. Department of Energy (not foldered) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - H.R. 2883 (blue folder), 1998 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Hearing on oversight of Federal property (blue folder), 1998 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Letters from Bezis regarding Washington's birthday (1998); letters regarding multiple bills / projects (not foldered) (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - CCA (Corrections Corporation of America) letter, June 20, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail; letters to and from Davis seeking support (not foldered), 1998 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Report of the Fairfax County Community Initiative to Reduce Youth Violence, November 1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Government Waste, Fraud, and Error Reduction Act of 1998 (blue folder) (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - TMD (Tom Davis) clips (Newspaper clippings), 1998 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Letters regarding Housing: LIHTC (Low-income Housing Tax Credit), American Community Renewal Act, H.R. 979, HOPWA (Housing opportunities for People with AIDS) (not foldered), 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - American Lung Association, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Philip Morris, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - correspondence regarding tobacco, USDA (United States Department of Agriculture), anti-sugar, discrimination (not foldered), 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous housing, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - H.R. 716. (Freedom From Government Competition Act of 1997) (blue folder), March 1998. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 716. (Freedom From Government Competition Act of 1997) (large accordian folder), 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - OGRC (Committee on Oversight and Government Reform) Power lines hearing (accordian folder), April 2007 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Power lines, Meadow Brook, Loudoun 500kV line, November 2006 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Energy: 500kV line, Federal; Letters; SCC (State Corporation Commission); PJM; Hearing; Press; PEC (Piedmont Environmental Council); FERC; Maps; Hazel (Til); Allegheney Energy; Dominion Valley; Monday, Site tour PEC, 2006-2007 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Cosponsored Bills, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Signed letters, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Somatic cell, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Franked pieces, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Franked mail, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Franked mail, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Franked phone calls, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Thrift supervision / Hunter Mill, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Postal Service, Eskridge Road Realignment, Merrifield, Virginia, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Vietnam pressed, June 2007 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Earthlink forbearance, Circa 2006 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Conservation easements, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Mantua, storage tanks, October 2007 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Local Radio Freedom Act, October 2007 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Anthrax hearing, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Hepatitis C hearing, 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 2631, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - FCC (Federal Communications Commission) letters, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - TELRIC (FCC's total element long-run incremental cost), 2002 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Nextwave / Verizon Hr, November 2002 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - WiFi Bill, March 7, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Triennial Review, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Verizon 271 / FCC Hr, October-November 2002 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Homeland Committee, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - HJ Res 96, Metro, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 25)